International Brotherhood of Painters & Allied Trades, Local 677, Glaziers & Glass Workers Minutes 5850
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Brotherhood of Painters & Allied Trades, Local 677, Glaziers & Glass Workers Minutes
1938-1975
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades, Local 677
5850
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Minutes (administrative records).
5713673
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 20, 2015
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Scope and Contents
Part of the "Van Arsdale Project"
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4212: Kheel Center Current Documents Correspondence /4296: ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office (New York, N.Y.) Training Manuals 5538: James C. Hill Arbitration Files 5588: David L. Cole Papers 5609: Philip Ross Collection of NLRB Documents 5712: Burton B. Turkus Arbitration Files 5780/209: ILGWU Research Department Records 5850: International Brotherhood of Painters & Allied Trades, Local 677, Glaziers & Glass Workers Minutes 6046: Archives Union File (AUF) 6178/008: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 8) 6178/016: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 16)
Painters, Industrial -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- Rochester; Building trades -- Employees -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- Rochester; Van Arsdale, Harry, 1905-1986.; International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades; International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades. Glazier and Glass Workers. Local 677 (Rochester, N.Y.)
5713673
- Minutes of the Glaziers and Glass Workers Local 677 (International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades), Rochester, New York, 1938-1975 (Box 1)
  - Minute Book 1: May 3, 1938 - May 6, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minute Book 2: May 6, 1941 - April 4, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minute Book 3: April, 18, 1944 - June 3, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Minute Book 4 - June 15, 1948 - December 19, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Minute Book 4: January 2, 1951 - February 15, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Minute Book 5: March 1, 1955 - December 1, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Minute Book 5: January 5, 1960 - September 8, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Minute Book 6: October 6, 1964 - December 1, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Minute Book 6: January 5, 1970 - September 8, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)